{
    "id": "c956817da95347779fc00c6370d41f39",
    "title": "Intermediate Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wish I ................................ better.",
            "description": "We use a past tense after I wish to talk about our wishes.",
            "answers": [
                "look",
                "looked",
                "have looked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I .................................. taller.",
            "description": "We use a past tense after I wish to talk about our wishes.",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "was",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I do have some regrets. I wish I ................................... harder.",
            "description": "We use past perfect after I wish to talk about unfulfilled past wishes.",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "have worked",
                "had worked"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "My mother ..................................... knit beautiful sweaters.",
            "description": "We use can to talk about ability.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... drive four wheelers.",
            "description": "We use can to mean 'know how to'.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "is able to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We will ........................................... reach there on time.",
            "description": "We cannot use can after will.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "be able to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How much time can you devote ...................................... English?",
            "description": "Devote is followed by to + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to learn",
                "to learning",
                "learning"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope that date is not set in ................................",
            "description": "If a date is set in stone, it cannot be changed.",
            "answers": [
                "slab",
                "rock",
                "stone"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a busy man without ..................................... patience.",
            "description": "Patience is an uncountable noun. We use much before uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "plenty of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ............................... better mend your ways.",
            "description": "Had better refers to the present and future. There is no such thing as have better.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is my number just ......................................... you would like to keep in touch with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "in case",
                "in case of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ........................................ time with you.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after enjoy.",
            "answers": [
                "spending",
                "to spend",
                "to spending"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}